https://www.goldenskate.com/privacy/

Oceania
U.S.
--Oceania
--U.S.
Figure Skating: Ladies and the Quad Jump
Russia’s Sinitsina and Katsalapov: ‘We are very excited to come back!’
Yuma Kagiyama commands men’s event; snatches NHK Trophy gold
Komatsubara and Koleto dance to first Grand Prix title at 2020 NHK Trophy
Tweet
Golden Skate has created this privacy policy to demonstrate it’s firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information.
COPPA
In order to comply with COPPA Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) of 1998, Golden Skate requires that all users must be 13 years or older at the time they sign up for an account. During the registration process, you agree to our Terms of Use. Part of that agreement is an affirmative statement that you are 13 or older.
Information we collect
Information we collect on the site may include (depending on what you provide):
username – your real name is only used if you provide it
email address – your email address is not shared nor can it be viewed by the public
IP address – your IP address is not shared nor can it be viewed by the public
How your personal information is used
For the purposes of allowing you to become a registered member so that you can participate in our discussion forums
We may use your email to contact you regarding updates to our site.
Your IP address is used for the purposes of analytics and tracking the number of visitors to our site.
Other information may include technical information regarding the browser and/or type of device you’re using which assists us in maintaining a user-friendly experience across the site.
Sharing, Using and Securing Data
Golden Skate is committed to ensuring that any information you provide to us is secure. We never sell or give any access to your data (or our servers that store your data) to anyone. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes, provided that you have given us your permission.
Cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This, however, may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensor and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.
Advertising
Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Google Adsense
Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads
Why did you receive an email from Golden Skate?
If you received an email from Golden Skate, (a) your email address is either listed with Golden Skate as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future, or (b) you have registered or otherwise have an existing relationship with Golden Skate and/or it’s contents. Golden Skate respects your time and attention by controlling the frequency of it’s mailings.
NOTE: Emails can appear to be sent from goldenskate.com when in fact they were NOT.
Please carefully examine the headers of the offending email to locate the IP address of the host that sent the email.
If an examination of the headers reveals that the message originated from a host in the goldenskate.com domain, then forward the message (with full headers) to the webmaster.
How can you stop receiving email from Golden Skate?
Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from Golden Skate, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions contained in any email.
If you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to the webmaster for review.
Personal Data and Removal
You have the right to request a copy of the personal data that we have on you. You also have a right to have your personal data removed, however, this does not include content that you have contributed unless there is personal data contained in that content.
GS Newsletter
Email address:
Leave this field empty if you're human:
Did You Know?
Maribel Vinson-Owen (October 12, 1911 – February 15, 1961) set the record for nine U.S. ladies’ figure skating titles which Michelle Kwan matched in 2005. As a single skater, she was the 1932 Olympic bronze medalist and a two-time World medalist (1928 silver, 1930 bronze). Vinson-Owen (as a coach) and her two daughters were part of the United States figure skating team that tragically died on Sabena Flight 548.
Recent News
Figure Skating: Ladies and the Quad Jump
It was three-time world silver medalist...
Russia’s Sinitsina and Katsalapov: ‘We are very excited to come back!’
Last season, Russian ice dancers Victoria...
Yuma Kagiyama commands men’s event; snatches NHK Trophy gold
Yuma Kagiyama of Japan dominated the...
Komatsubara and Koleto dance to first Grand Prix title at 2020 NHK Trophy
Misato Komatsubara and Tim Koleto maintained...
Figure Skating Events
« December 2020
»
2020 British Inclusive Skating Virtual International Championships
U.S.
Copyright © Golden Skate.
